I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
-I'm thinking of quitting this life.
-Is it because of a woman?
Yeah, well...
Tanaka-kun! Tanaka-kun!
Uhh...
Page 31.
Thanks.
"Classical Japanese"
"The color of the flowers
of the twin sal trees
"Classical Japanese"
is a manifestation of the saying,
"All that prosper must decline."
"Classical Japanese"
Good for you, Tanaka!
However, this is your English period.
Quiet down!
How long is this life going to continue?
At the age of 14,
my life was at a dead end.
That is...until I met him.
"Live 1: The View at Fourteen"
This is a message from
your Student Council.
The equipment used by the
various clubs should be stored-
Tanabe, did you read that article?
Yeah. Isn't that something?
The first batter up,
and in the major league, too!
Yeah...
The way our lives have been,
we'll never be able to write
an interesting autobiography.
Hey, Tanaka...
Are you living your life
to write an autobiography?
Of course not. But...
Let's enjoy life! C'mon!
Hey, Tanabe!
-C'mon, Yoshida-kun!
-Have you gained weight, Kazuko?
Listen, I shortened my
100-meter time by two seconds!
I found this great shaved ice shop.
Why don't we go?
Don't splash me!
Oh, this is great!
This is good! It's good! It's good!
Oh! It's Ishiguro-sempai!
A beautiful face and dynamite body!
A great athlete and her grades
are always in the top ten!
Izumi Ishiguro's the perfect
Miss Higashi Middle School!
She gets me hot all over! I can't stand it!
-You're next!
-Okay!
Okay...I'm gonna snap away...
I'll sell 'em all and make me a fortune!
Hey! What are you doing?!
I see. You want to take some too?
Is that it?
Back then, Izumi-chain was
the first person to talk to me.
"Thank you for your years of patronage.
Nakajima Calligraphy School"
"Tenant Wanted"
-Izumi-chan...
-Give it back!
Until three years ago,
that's what I called her.
Someone's over there!
See?! There are two guys over there!
Who are they?! 7th graders?!
Somebody you know, Izumi?
-They had a camera, those two.
-Catch them!
Koyuki?
Man, they got a good look at us.
Come on. Let's go to the game center.
Hurry up, Tanaka!
Hey, stop that!
Get lost!
Yeah, that's it! Go!
Thanks!
Did it! The Golden Bat!
-Wanna eat a beef bowl?
-I'll pass. I'm broke.
I see. See ya!
This place seems a little iffy...
Whaddya want?!
Ouch...
Oww...
Man...
What am I doing?
Oww!
Yay! Now it's my turn! Hold him!
You can't get away from us!
Wait!
Damn!
What's with that dog?!
Hey, what are you doing?
Quit tormenting the dog!
Aw, shut up! Let's get outta here!
Yeah!
Beck! Come here!
I told you, you shouldn't go out alone.
You...You made me worried.
That guy's...a foreigner?
Doesn't this dog look weird?
No, no...Not bad dog...
Huh? You're Japanese?
Thanks for saving Beck.
Doggy...Come here, doggy.
Good boy...
Uh-uh. You shouldn't put your hand out
to a frightened dog.
-Use these.
-Thanks.
See ya.
"Onochin Loans"
(This is a pack of tissues)
I'll return this to you next time!
Is that for real?
Yeah. First I get punched,
and then I get bitten...What a day!
No way...That's awful!
That weird dog...I hope
it doesn't have rabies.
Hey! There's someone here
to see you, Tanaka!
It's Ishiguro-sempai!
Uhh...Don't let them bother you.
Listen, are you free on Saturday, Koyuki?
Huh?!
What happened? You get into a fight?
It's nothing. I'm perfectly fine now.
Listen, Koyuki...
There was another boy
with the same name as me,
Yukio Tanaka, in our calligraphy class.
So Izumi-chan gave me
the nickname Koyuki.
(Ko = little)
That's why she calls me Koyuki.
"Koyuki"
I'm going bowling with some friends.
Won't you come with us?
Yeah...
Oh, good. Now we have enough people.
It's almost exam time, so it's
hard getting everyone to join in.
I didn't want to waste
the coupon Kayo-chan gave me.
Koyuki...Thanks.
Yeah...
Oh, I have P.E. Next. See you Saturday!
I can't believe it...
You're telling me...
-You seem to be happy.
-Yeah, well...
-Don't stay out too late, now!
-I won't.
The uptown-bound train
will be pulling in to track two.
Please wait behind the yellow line.
Wait behind the yellow line!
Yay! I got a strike!
Nice, Izumi-chan!
We'll never win at this rate!
Come on, Izumi. Let's switch teams.
Koyuki...
Try aiming at those marks in front of you.
Yay! Alright!
Pretty good advice, don't you think?
Oh, no. It's me...My talent.
Yay!
You're pretty good, Koyuki!
-Yes!
-Good job!
At that moment, the two years
we hadn't seen each other...
...vanished completely.
Boy, am I hungry!
-Let's go to McDonald's!
-How about Mr. Donut?
I'd rather have a Yoshinoya beef bowl.
-Huh?!
What do I want?
I'll go by myself...
Oh! Kayo-chan!
Kayo-chan!
Oh, Izumichi!
Yeah!
What are you doing?
We're trying to decide whether
to go to McDonald's or Yoshinoya.
McDonald's!
I'm not hungry. Let's go somewhere else.
Kayo-chan, you're reeking of alcohol...
-I hear it's pretty good.
-No way...
Oh, come on...
Yay!
Are you drinking, Koyuki-kun?
Yes. I'm on my second glass
of oolong tea.
Shall we all go for karaoke?
I'll pass. I've never been to a
karaoke place, and I'm out of money.
But Izumichi was raving
about your singing...
Here you go! It's on the house, kids!
Oh, Mit-chan...Did you
have a chef's license?
'Course not.
-What's Mit-chan-san's real name?
-Why?
I want to thank him,
but I don't think a kid like me
should be calling him Mit-chan...
Why, I don't mind you calling me Mit-chan.
Thanks for the food, Mit-chan-san!
You know, we have a lot of regulars,
but none of them knows
what the others do.
They don't even know if their names
are real or just nicknames.
It's Remedy's policy not
to bring problems in here.
But that means you're breaking up with me!
As I said, I don't have the time.
Oh, man...
Damn you, Ryusuke...
He's called Ryusuke. Mature for 16.
-You know him?
-Uhh...no...
He's the worst...Making girls cry,
not paying back money he owes...
No way...
But, how can I put it?
He has a strange attraction
for other people, that Ryusuke.
-Besides, he's always bluffing.
-Mit-chan, sake!
Bluffing?
Koyuki, have you heard of Dying Breed?
There's this super popular band
called Dying Breed in America.
What about Dying Breed? I love them!
He says he used to play in a band
with Eddy, Dying Breed's guitarist.
Who are you talking about?
You idiot...
Come on. You've got
other guys besides me.
Ryusuke! Which is more important
to you?! Me or the band?!
The band.
Mit-chan-san...Would you give this to him?
Sure...
Wasn't it like a drama back there?
Yeah. It was really something.
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Come look at this!
Somebody really did a job on this car.
It's gonna cost a mint to fix it.
Sempai, I don't think
you should get too close.
What is it? Killjoy.
Hey! What the fuck are
you doing to my car?!
Whatsa matter, you fuckers around
here speak English, or what?
Oh...I'm...sorry...
Sempai! Why are you apologizing?!
W-well...
-You leaving?
-Yeah...
A young kid asked me to give this to you.
To me? Thanks, Mit-chan.
Fuckin' stupid little kids!
I'm gonna make you pay
for all of this right now!
No, no. We are not guilty. We-
What are you, a rapper or a singer?
"We are the world?!"
I'll kick your ass if you don't pay!
I'm serious. Shut the...
...fuck up!
Back off, damn you!
Koyuki...
Don't act big just because
you're overgrown, dumbass (baka yaro)!
Ba...ka?
Nobody calls me baka around here!
You little shit! I'm kicking
your fucking ass, man! Right about now!
Stop it!
I saw your car two hours ago
and it was already scratched.
Who the hell are you?!
You should apologize to these kids.
What the fuck?!
Apologize.
Apologize!
The police are right there.
Shut the fuck up, kid!
Here, let's get somewhere else.
Come on!
Come on, he says...
Ryusuke-kun!
Never mind me. Get on home.
"Noodles"
Here are your ramen noodles.
This looks good!
But those French fries...
Weren't they just awful?
You haven't finished your ramen.
Yeah...But I really want
to eat a beef bowl!
Koyuki...
Hey, hey-hey hey!
I-It's cool, man. It's cool.
Put that thing down, man, please.
Put it down. Take it easy.
Please...
Well...Wanna try?
I don't know about your town,
but my friends in New York died.
You can't fuck around in my neighborhood.
Get the fuck outta here! Fucking bastard!
-No! No! Leave it!
-Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Ryusuke-kun!
Damn...Treating me like trash...
Shit!
R-Ryusuke-kun! Are you all right?!
They were so drunk, I didn't
think they'd figure it out.
Man...it hurts...
I was impressed.
You're such a shorty, but you
went after those big foreigners.
What's the matter?
Hey, hey...I'm the one
who should be crying.
I'm sorry. But lately...
for a long time, actually,
I felt like no one cared if I lived or not.
Koyuki!
It's them...
Hey, you guys-
-Are you all right?
-I'm just scratched up.
The other day, he saved my dog.
Your dog?
Beck is a dog Eddy and I found
when we were in a band together.
-Oh, so that's a true story?
-Oh, sorry Koyuki-kun.
-Sorry I'm so late.
-Yeah...
I love the Dying Breed!
Oh? Then why don't you come
and see our band sometime?
Yes! I will! That's so exciting!
Matt of Dying Breed is really funny.
If he doesn't have a drink before
a show he can't get up on the stage.
That looks pretty weird to me.
Now I'm pretty worried...
for Ishiguro-sempai.
I don't give a damn about you, though.
So cheer up...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
This is Ryusuke-kun's address...
Okay...Shall we barge in on him?
Huh? Right now?
Koyuki...What kind of music
do you listen to?
-Chiemi Kuniyoshi.
-Kuniyoshi? Oh, that idol singer?
Yeah...I'm sure she's going
to break out soon.
I think it's this way.
Maybe...
And, after taking a lot of wrong turns,
we finally arrived at Ryusuke-kun's home.
"Fishing"
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Rock, you see, is the
vibration of the soul. Hm?
"Next Episode"
Rock, you see, is the
vibration of the soul. Hm?
"Next Episode"